[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it possible to see around corners?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of phobia is defined as fear of high places?", "correct_answer": "Acrophobia", "incorrect_answers": ["Tapephobia", "Xenophobia", "Botophobia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the other common name of the plant Prunus avium, better known as Sweet cherry?", "correct_answer": "Wild cherry", "incorrect_answers": ["Blood cherry", "All of these", "Crimson cherry"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the first web browser that had both graphics and text?", "correct_answer": "Mosaic", "incorrect_answers": ["Bob the Dog", "Tillie", "Gopher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tomato juice is the official beverage of this state in the USA.", "correct_answer": "Ohio", "incorrect_answers": ["Colorado", "Texas", "California"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1915, the great American baseball player of the 1920s, Babe Ruth, hit his first home against which team?", "correct_answer": "The Yankees", "incorrect_answers": ["The Red Stockings", "The White Sox", "The Red Sox"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This fine character, who played Coffer in The Wild Bunch, is best known as the Warden in Cool Hand Luke.", "correct_answer": "Strother Martin", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Jeter", "Steve Martin", "Ernest Borgnine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Andy collect in the comedy The 40-Year-Old Virgin?", "correct_answer": "action figures", "incorrect_answers": ["comic books", "movie paraphernalia", "video games"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Addis Ababa is the capital of what country?", "correct_answer": "Ethiopia", "incorrect_answers": ["Samoa", "Paraguay", "Ghana"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What US state is known as the Peach State?", "correct_answer": "Georgia", "incorrect_answers": ["Louisiana", "Montana", "Connecticut"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is a common nickname for the Yorkshire Terriers?", "correct_answer": "Yorkie", "incorrect_answers": ["They have no nickname.", "Yorkle", "Shorky"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "2000s Girlfight was Michelle Rodriguezs breakout role.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]